

- +506 83044195
- San José, Costa Rica
- in https://linkedin.com/in/jrodvi
- https://github.com/jrodvi
- % https://jrodriguezv.net

ABOUT ME

I've been working as a software developer for more than 12 years on Frontend and Backend projects.

I've worked as an analyst and programmer, using different technologies and platforms, having worked mainly on Backend projects in recent years.

SKILLS

Teamwork

Adapatability

Continuous learning

Autonomy

TECH SKILLS

C#	Vue.js	RabbitMQ
JavaScript	Bootstrap	Quartz.NET
TypeScript	ASP.Net	Hibernate
T-SQL	MVC	SpringBoot
PL/SQL	EF	MongoDB
HTML5	Dapper	RavenDB
CSS ₃	Polly	MS SQL Server
Java	Swagger	MySQL
Node.is	MassTransit	Oracle database

EDUCATION

Software Engineering

CENFOTEC

In progress

Scrum Master Certificate

International Scrum Institute 2013

Software Development Technician CENFOTEC

2010

EXPERIENCE

Senior Software Developer

Data Collection Trades (2018 – present)

- Analyze user requirements, design the domain model, and code the application or backend module.
- Integrate external to systems to company systems.
- Deploy the different software components developed.

Senior Software Developer

UST-Global (2016 – 2018)

- Analyze user requirements, design the domain model, and code the application.
- Develop frontend and backend of web applications related to the financial and retail areas and code their corresponding unit tests.
- Configure and deploy .Net web applications to Azure and application servers such as IIS.
- Define and estimate the tasks for the team (as technical lead).
- Follow Scrum methodology.

Developer Analyst

Exceltec Business Solution (2014 – 2016)

- Develop web application for room reservation working with Exchange
 Web Services and iCalendar format.
- Develop web application for configuration of automatic maintenance of databases that allows build T-SQL through the UI.